Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Water Pressure Study in Clarkston, Washington (Box 32, Folder 1390)
- Market Survey of the Industrial Uses of Wheat in the Pacific Northwest (Box 32, Folder 1391)
- Literature Search on Utilization of Sawdust and Shaving 1393 (Box 32, Folder 1392)
- Dr. Claude Weitz Spectrographic Analysis of Car Liver and Kidney (Box 32, Folder 1393)
- Water Analysis and Corrosion (Box 32, Folder 1394)
- Arson Investigation, Wenatchee (Box 32, Folder 1395)
- Arson Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1396)
- West Kootenay Power and Light Company, Ltd. Dumping of 5/8" Diameter Steel Span (Box 32, Folder 1397)
- Carbon Dating-4 Hawaiian Samples (Box 32, Folder 1398)
- Econonic Study of the use of Mineral Products in Wood Technology (Box 32, Folder 1399)
- Bibliography of Washington Minerals (Box 32, Folder 1400)
- Bibliography of Cements and Adhesives (Box 32, Folder 1401)
- A Survey of Water Resource Quality in Washington State (Box 32, Folder 1402)
- Possible Uses of Minerals in Forest Product Manufacture (Box 32, Folder 1403)
- Determination of Strychnine (Box 32, Folder 1404)
- Analyze Aviation Gas (Box 32, Folder 1405)
- Fire Test on Laminated Beams (Box 32, Folder 1406)
- Fire Test on Laminated Beams (Box 32, Folder 1407)
- Corrosive Character of Municipal and Industrial Waters of the State of Washington (Box 32, Folder 1408)
- Purchase Specifications for Paints - WSC and Washington State (Box 32, Folder 1409)
- Interagency Water Basic Data Program (Box 32, Folder 1410)
- Determination of Resin in Wood Products (Box 32, Folder 1411)
- Water Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1412)
- Forensic Investigation (Box 32, Folder 1413)
- Bulletin on Domestic Water (Box 32, Folder 1414)
- **U.S. Navy Bureau of Ship Res. Project Review and Information Exchange Program (Box 32, Folder 1415)
- Case Studies of Contract Research by Small Manufacturers (Box 32, Folder 1416)
- Evaluation of Aluminum Foil Glue Bonds (Box 32, Folder 1417)
- Yakima Pipe Network Analysis (Box 32, Folder 1418)
- Laboratory Filter Rental (Box 32, Folder 1419)
- Umpqua River Estuary Model (Box 33, Folder 1420)
- Biochemical Responses of Plant Tissues of HF Fumigation (Box 33, Folder 1421)
- Biochemical Response of Plant Tissue to HF Fumigation (Box 33, Folder 1422)
- Lininological Study of Anaerobic-Aerobic Sewage Ponds (Box 33, Folder 1423)
- Analysis of Organic Pesticides by Gas Chromatology (Box 33, Folder 1424)
- Hydraulic Laboratory Development of Stream Gaging Stations (Box 33, Folder 1425)
- Seismic Investigations in the Reynolds Creek Experimental Watershed (Box 33, Folder 1426)
- Boron and Tin Analysis of Hair, Nails and Arteries (Box 33, Folder 1427)
- Trace Element Analysis of Biological Samples (Box 33, Folder 1428)
- Walla Walla Lagoon Effluent Quality Examination (Box 33, Folder 1429)
- Preparing Pea Flour Extender Source (Box 33, Folder 1430)
- Gamma Ray Sterilization of Pine Moth Larvae (Box 33, Folder 1431)
- Analysis of Spinels (Box 33, Folder 1432)
- Analysis of Blood Samples for Volatile Acids (Box 33, Folder 1433)
- Soils Tests on Comptom Union Building Addition (Box 33, Folder 1434)
- Analysis of Aluminum Single Crystals for Carbon (Box 33, Folder 1435)
- Gas-Chromatographic Analysis of Rumen Fluids (Box 33, Folder 1436)
- Radiocarbon Dating of Charcoal Sample (Box 33, Folder 1437)
- Freeze Drying of Solutions (Box 33, Folder 1438)
- Noise Reduction Progress in Fulmer Hall (Box 33, Folder 1439)
- Gamma Ray Sterilization of Pine Moth Larvae (Box 33, Folder 1440)
- Drying Time Analysis on Paint Sample (Box 33, Folder 1441)
- Neutron Activation Analysis of Bone Ash (Box 33, Folder 1442)
- Laminate Cards (Box 33, Folder 1443)
- Preliminary Design (Box 33, Folder 1444)
- Food Property Measurements by Acoustic and Vibration Analysis (Box 33, Folder 1445)
- Age Date Wood Samples (Box 33, Folder 1446)
- Age Date Shell Samples (Box 33, Folder 1447)
- Fluoride and Calcium Effects on Bone and Teeth (Box 33, Folder 1448)
- Analyze Changes to a Clarinet (Box 33, Folder 1449)
- Suspect Drug Sample (Box 33, Folder 1450)
- Radiocarbon Age Dating of Charcoal (Box 33, Folder 1451)
- Prank Explosion (Box 33, Folder 1452)
- RadQarbon Dating of Archeological Materials (Box 33, Folder 1453)
- Investigation of Tile Bonding (Box 33, Folder 1454)
- Determination of Volatile Fatty Acids in Ensilage (Box 33, Folder 1455)
- Semiquantitative Spectrochemical Analysis of Glass Beads (Box 33, Folder 1456)
- Carbon Dating of Charcoal Samples (Box 33, Folder 1457)
- Freeze Dry Flowers (Box 33, Folder 1458)
- Analysis of Two Solid Substances (Box 33, Folder 1459)
- Spectrographic Analysis of Speech (Box 33, Folder 1460)
- Ozette Village Carbon-14 Dating (Box 33, Folder 1461)
- Food Property Measurement by Acoustic Analysis (Box 33, Folder 1462)
- Run IR Spectra (Box 33, Folder 1463)
- Trace Element Analysis of Potatoes (Box 33, Folder 1464)
- Police Investigation (Box 33, Folder 1465)
- Evaluation of Exterior Paints for B and G (Box 33, Folder 1466)
- Date Soil Samples (Box 33, Folder 1467)
- Design and Construct a Six-Meter Calorimeter (Box 33, Folder 1468)
- Use of Differential Scanning Calorimeter (Box 33, Folder 1469)
- WSU college Research Fund (Box 33, Folder 1470)
- Mode of Atmospheric Uptake by Foliage (Box 33, Folder 1471)
- Writing Highway Legislation (Box 33, Folder 1472)
- Carbon-14 Dating (Box 33, Folder 1473)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Specimen (Box 33, Folder 1474)
- Radiocarbon Dating of Archeological Material (Box 33, Folder 1475)
- Freeze Dry Horse Heads (Box 33, Folder 1476)
- Trace Element Analysis Water (Box 33, Folder 1477)
- Highway Interim Committee Studies (1959-1961) (Box 33, Folder 1478)
- Highway Interim Committee Studies (1961-1963) (Box 33, Folder 1479)
- Highway Legislation Research Studies (Box 33, Folder 1480)
- Washington State Highway Commission - Preliminary Investigation of Garden Springs (Box 33, Folder 1481)
- Highway Legislature Studies (Box 33, Folder 1482)
- Police Investigation - Wenatchee, Washington (Box 33, Folder 1483)
- Evaluation of Factors Affecting Stream Self-purification (Box 33, Folder 1484)
- Ground Water Recharge in Basalt (Box 33, Folder 1485)
- Planning and Evaluation Project (Box 33, Folder 1486)
- Special Investigation for Washington Testing Laboratories (Box 33, Folder 1487)
- Analysis of Hog Feed for Toxic Components (Box 33, Folder 1488)
- Response and Fatigue of 56" Sphere on 3/8 EAS Steel Spam (Box 33, Folder 1489)
- Investigation of Deposits in Water Pipes (Box 33, Folder 1490)
- Polymer Grafting on Wheat (Box 33, Folder 1491)
- Evaluation of Elements in Inorganic and Organic Food (Box 33, Folder 1492)
- Causes of Anomalous Carbon-14 Dates in Pacific Island Archeology (Box 33, Folder 1493)
- Density Control with Nuclear Equipment (Box 33, Folder 1494)
- Geophysical Studies for Whitman County, Washington (Box 33, Folder 1495)
- Calibration Tests (Box 33, Folder 1496)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Floating Backwaters (Box 33, Folder 1497)
- Infra-red Radiation for Lumber Drying (Box 33, Folder 1498)
- Floor Systems for Low-rise Appartments (Box 33, Folder 1499)
- An Infra-red Temperature Monitor for Lumber Drying (Box 33, Folder 1500)
- A Market Survey of the Industrial Uses of Wheat in the Paper and Plywood Industries (1962/1963) (Box 33, Folder 1501)
- A Market Survery of the Industrial (Box 33, Folder 1502)
- Moisture Relationship of Wood at High Temperatures (Box 33, Folder 1503)
- **Dynamic Strain the Pesoelectri Effect in Wood (Box 33, Folder 1504)
- Flour Blender (Box 33, Folder 1505)
- A Study of Mechanisms for Dividing Liquids into Fine Droplets (Box 33, Folder 1506)
- A.R.S. Flume Model (Box 33, Folder 1507)
- A.R.S. Flume Model (Box 33, Folder 1508)
- Referee Water Analysis (Box 33, Folder 1509)
- Development of Molding Procedure and Molds for Plastic Items (Box 33, Folder 1510)
- Procedures and Molds for Plastic Items Progress Report (Box 33, Folder 1511)
- Accelerated Weathering of Various Coatings (Box 33, Folder 1512)
- Screen Analysis for a Road Aggregate (Box 33, Folder 1513)
- Seismic Calibration Test (Box 33, Folder 1514)
- 381 A6 (Box 33, Folder 1515)
- 381 A6.1 (Box 33, Folder 1516)
- **381 A6.2 College Patent Comm. (Box 33, Folder 1517)
- 381 A6.3 Dean and Directors Meetings (Box 33, Folder 1518)
- Air Conditioning for Small Animal Laboratory in Pakistan (Box 34, Folder 1519)
- Deception-Induced Fluctuations (Box 34, Folder 1520)
- Heat Pump Defrosting (Box 34, Folder 1521)
- The Effect of Variations in Compaction on the Strength of Cement Treated Bases (Box 34, Folder 1522)
- Pyrolytic Degradation of Complex Fluorides in Plant and Animal Tissue (Box 34, Folder 1523)
- Discussion of Proposed Fumigation Work this Summer Held May 20th, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 1524)
- Development of a Transistorized Amplifier for the MINI-ADAK (Box 34, Folder 1525)
- Unifine Flour Mill (Box 34, Folder 1526)
- Analysis of Finger Joint Design by Photoelastic Techniques (Box 34, Folder 1527)
- Conversion of Arabogalactan to Useful Product (Box 34, Folder 1528)
- Fundamentals of Zone Refining (Box 34, Folder 1529)
- Background Work in Fluidized Beds (Bolme) (Box 34, Folder 1530)
- Corrosion Irrigation Pipes (Box 34, Folder 1531)
- New Test for the Relative Permeability of Highway Shoulders (Box 34, Folder 1532)
- Analysis of Water Movement in Soils Using Ultrasonic Methods (Box 34, Folder 1533)
- Resistivity System Orientation (Box 34, Folder 1534)
- Seismic System Orientation (Box 34, Folder 1535)
- The Influence of Logging Operations on Runoff from Precipitation (Box 34, Folder 1536)
- The Development of a Precise Multiple Orifice Calibrating System (Box 34, Folder 1537)
- Movement of Ground Water in Crystalline Rocks (Box 34, Folder 1538)
- Development of a Hydrological Program (Box 34, Folder 1539)
- Study of Non-circular Conduits (Box 34, Folder 1540)
- Geochemical Investigation of Limestone in Stevens County, Washington (Box 34, Folder 1541)
- Application of Seismographic Techniques to Archeological Research (Box 34, Folder 1542)
- Crystallography and Characteristics of Low Temperature Martensitic Transformations (Box 34, Folder 1543)
- Beneficiation of Utibe Barite (Box 34, Folder 1544)
- Cle Elum - Blewett Pass Ore Utilization (Box 34, Folder 1545)
- Development of Analytical Methods for the Analysis of Hg, Sn and Ag, Using Diphenolthiurcarbazone (Box 34, Folder 1546)
- Stress Measurements of Confined Rock in and Near the Plastic Stage (Box 34, Folder 1547)
- Seismic System Orientation (Box 34, Folder 1548)
- Flotation of Chyrysocolla (Copper Silicate) (Box 34, Folder 1549)
- Purification of Zinc Electrolysis Solutions (Box 34, Folder 1550)
- Ocurrence of Beryllium in Washington and the Beneficiation of Same (Box 34, Folder 1551)
- Resistivity System Orientation (Box 34, Folder 1552)
- The Solubilizing of Metals by Sulfuric Acid Roasting (Box 34, Folder 1553)
- A Survey of Water Resources Quality in Washington State (Box 34, Folder 1554)
- Sewage Oxidation Ponds in Washington (Box 34, Folder 1555)
- Comparison of Coliform Determination Methods (Box 34, Folder 1556)
- Effect of Industrial Wastes on Anaerobic Digestion (Box 34, Folder 1557)
- Membership on Water Resources Advisory commission (Box 34, Folder 1558)
- Sewage Plant Operators Manual (Box 34, Folder 1559)
- Sulphite Waste Treatment (Box 34, Folder 1560)
- **Washington State Regional School Lab. (Box 34, Folder 1561)
- Architectural Research Projects Analysis (Box 34, Folder 1562)
- Spiral Grain Patterns in Coniferous Trees (Box 34, Folder 1563)
- Efficiency Studies of Wood Beams (Box 34, Folder 1564)
- Rapid Laminating of Beams by Preheat Method (Box 34, Folder 1565)
- Resin Impregnated Flake Products (Box 34, Folder 1566)
- "Dimensional Stabilization of Glued Wood Products by Mechanical Means" - Paper by GGM (Box 34, Folder 1567)
- Non-Destructive Testing of Adhesive Prodcuts (Box 34, Folder 1568)
- Fundamentals of Adhesion (Box 34, Folder 1569)
- Properties of New Adhesives (Box 34, Folder 1570)
- Physical Properties of Inland-type Douglas Fir (Box 34, Folder 1571)
- Mechanical Properties of Wood Fiber (Box 34, Folder 1572)
- Sorption Phenomena in Wood (Box 34, Folder 1573)
- Potential Resulting from Pressure Gradients in Liquids (Box 34, Folder 1574)
- Special - Purpose Digital Computer for Random Walk Problems (Box 34, Folder 1575)
- Microbiologic Conversion of Arabolactan to Useful Products (Box 34, Folder 1576)
- Industrial Carbon Survey - Pocatello, Idaho (Box 34, Folder 1577)
- Fundamental Processes in Lubricating Bearing Surfaces (Box 34, Folder 1578)
- (Revised) Survey of Rare Earth, Trorium, and Minor Elements in the State of Washington (Box 34, Folder 1579)
- Processing Monomer-impreganted Wood Samples (Box 34, Folder 1580)
- Economic Feasibility Study on Flume Retardant Wood (Box 34, Folder 1581)
- Acoustical Evaluation of Construction Products (Box 34, Folder 1582)
- Study of Basic Stress Values for Lock-Deck (Box 34, Folder 1583)
- Study Agreement: Corrosion Investigation (Box 34, Folder 1584)
- Geophysical Well Logging (Box 34, Folder 1585)
- Gasoline Analysis (Box 34, Folder 1586)
- Analysis of Sewer Gas (Box 34, Folder 1587)
- Evaluation of Ground Water Survey (Box 34, Folder 1588)
- Surface Resistance of Plane Boundaries Roughened with Discrete Geometric Shapes (Box 34, Folder 1589)
- Sound Suppressor Model Studies (Box 34, Folder 1590)
- Analysis of Water Distribution Network Using Mcllroy Analyzer (Box 34, Folder 1591)
- Survey of Industrial Research in the Northwest (Box 34, Folder 1592)
- Highway Test Track Development and Operation (Box 34, Folder 1593)
- Development of Suitable Working Stresses for Structural Lumber Used in Tension (Box 34, Folder 1594)
- Prototype Computer for Vibration Testing Machine (Box 34, Folder 1595)
- Study of Efficiency of Floating Breakwaters Constructed of Logs (Box 34, Folder 1596)
- Develop Corrosion Resistant Anchor Rods for Grant County Conditions (Box 34, Folder 1597)
- Study of Accelerants in Fire Remains (Box 34, Folder 1598)
- Photographic Work for R.M. Haleen (Box 34, Folder 1599)
- Carbon Dating (Box 34, Folder 1600)
- Consultation of Research Project (Box 34, Folder 1601)
- Resin as a Plywood Adhesive (Box 34, Folder 1602)
- Analysis of Teco Report on Plant Trial of CP59 at Forrest Industries, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 1603)
- Evaluation of CP59 as a Binder for Particleboard (Box 34, Folder 1604)
- Preliminary Report on Plant Trial of CP59 at Forrest Industries, Inc. (Box 34, Folder 1605)
- Evaluation of CP59 as a Binder for Particleboard (Box 34, Folder 1606)
- Flow Distribution Analysis for Water System (Box 34, Folder 1607)
- Umpire Analysis of Four Samples of Gold Ore (Box 34, Folder 1608)
- Study on Adsorption and Retention of Chemical Compounds by High Density Polyethylene (Box 34, Folder 1609)
- Studies on a Reusable Plastic Milk Container Progress Report #6 (Box 34, Folder 1610)
- Studies on a Reusable Plastic Milk Container Progress Report #5 (Box 34, Folder 1610)
- Development and Construction of a 250Kv Surge Generator (Box 34, Folder 1611)
- Corrosion Prevention Study on Power Transformers (Box 34, Folder 1613)
- Optimization of Bagasse Board Manufacture (Box 34, Folder 1614)
- Evaluation of Chicken-Litter as Raw Material for Bagasses Boards (Box 34, Folder 1615)
- Analytical Studies on Warping of Bagasse Boards (Box 34, Folder 1616)
- Study of Resin Application Techniques (Box 34, Folder 1617)
- A comparison of Resin (Box 34, Folder 1618)
- A Comparison of Resin Application Techniques (Box 34, Folder 1619)
- Water Reclamation by Reverse Osmosis (Box 34, Folder 1620)
- **Health Research Facilities Matching - Moveable Scientific Equipment (Box 34, Folder 1621)
- Kraft Mill Odor and Objectionability Thresholds (Box 34, Folder 1622)
- The Ecology of Chromatium in Sewage Ponds (Box 34, Folder 1623)
- Occurrence of Pesticides in Aquatic Environment (Box 34, Folder 1624)
- The Effect of Benthos in Decomposition (Box 34, Folder 1625)
- Heat Capacity and Heat of Mixing Measurements on Sea Water (Box 34, Folder 1626)
- Spillway Characteristics for Fish Passage (Box 34, Folder 1627)
- Development of a Shoe Reconditioner (Box 34, Folder 1628)
- Effect of Compression Wood in Particleboard Sandwell and Co., Ltd. (Box 34, Folder 1629)
- Determination of Crushing Characteristics of a Feldspar Ore. (Box 34, Folder 1630)
- Police Investigation Burglary (Box 34, Folder 1631)
- Chemical and Spectrochemical Analyses of Silver Ore (Box 34, Folder 1632)
- Investigation of Gravity Separation of Silver Ore (Box 34, Folder 1633)
- Impurity Tests for Lubricating Oil (Box 34, Folder 1634)
- Twelve Megacycle Radio Propagation Experiments (Box 34, Folder 1635)
- Arson Investigation (Box 34, Folder 1636)
- Police Investigation (Box 34, Folder 1637)
- Fairbanks Water System Analysis (Box 34, Folder 1638)
- Flow Distribution Analysis of Moscow, Idaho Water System (Box 34, Folder 1639)
- Strain Gage Tests, Rocky Reach Trashrack (Box 34, Folder 1640)
- Cyanidation Beneficiation of California Gold Ore Amenability and Economic Recovery Tests (Box 34, Folder 1641)
- Effect of Irrigation Use on Quality of Return Water (Box 34, Folder 1642)
- X-ray Difraction Study of Ag-MnO Material (Box 34, Folder 1643)
- A Study of the Beneficiation of Asbestos Ores (Box 34, Folder 1644)
- Friction Control Fluid for Nylatron-Paper Interface (Box 34, Folder 1645)
- Irrigation Couplers (Box 34, Folder 1646)
- Trace Element Analysis of High Purity MgO (Box 34, Folder 1647)
- Investigation of Fuel Oil Contamination (Box 34, Folder 1648)
- Trans-Polar HF Radio Propagation Study U.S. Air Force Systems Communications (Box 34, Folder 1649)
- International Conference on Carbon 14 and Tritium Dating (Box 34, Folder 1650)
- **A Particle Board Mfg. Process in Ferry Co., Wn. (Box 34, Folder 1651)
- **Soil and Water Conservation Res. (Box 34, Folder 1652)
- Reynolds' Creek Seismic Studies (Box 34, Folder 1653)
- Study of Development and Commercial Introduction of Processes for Utilization of Wheat in Paper Products Industry (Box 34, Folder 1654)
- Investigation of Use and Manufacture of Wood Plastic Alloys (Box 35, Folder 1655)
- Hydrochloric Acid Project (Box 35, Folder 1656)
- **Study of Performance Std. and Quality Control Proc. for Impression Finger Machine (Box 35, Folder 1657)
- **Feasibility Study of Vibration Forming Machine (Box 35, Folder 1658)
- Police Investigation, Davenport, Washington (Box 35, Folder 1659)
- Prediction of Pressure in Reactor Cell as a Function of Time (Box 35, Folder 1660)
- Reactor Graphite Crushing Study (Box 35, Folder 1661)
- Mr. Rex E.E. Gjertson Investigation of Oil Sample (Box 35, Folder 1662)
- Water Distribution Analysis for Goldendale, Washington (Box 35, Folder 1663)
- Cooperative Photostress Determination of Stress in STar Mine (Box 35, Folder 1664)
- Vinsol in Dry Process, Medium Density Fiberboard (Box 35, Folder 1665)
- Police Investigation Adams County (Box 35, Folder 1666)
- Determine of Concentration Characteristics of Cenosite Ore (Box 35, Folder 1667)
- Evaluation of Mineral Sample (Box 35, Folder 1668)
- Brick Investigation (Box 35, Folder 1669)
- Trace Element Analysis of Alfalfa (Box 35, Folder 1670)
- Carbon Dating of Archeological Samples (Box 35, Folder 1671)
- Carbon Dating of Soil Samples (Box 35, Folder 1672)
- Laboratory Evaluation of Wood Products (Box 35, Folder 1673)
- **Study of S2S Hardboard Manufacture (525??) (Box 35, Folder 1674)
- **Preliminary Investigation of Triton Ionic Treater (Box 35, Folder 1675)
- Conference on Carbon-14 and Tritium Dating (Box 35, Folder 1676)
- Second Symposium on Non-destructive Testing of Wood (Box 35, Folder 1677)
- Vibration Fatigue Tests - Olin Compresto Conductors (Box 35, Folder 1678)
- Fatigue of 795 MCM Standard and Compresto Conductors (Box 35, Folder 1679)
- Effect of and RF Field on Neon Tube Life (Box 35, Folder 1680)
- Corrosion (Box 35, Folder 1681)
- Corrosion of Aluminum Pump in Washing Machine (Box 35, Folder 1682)
- Torque Characteristics of Oxidized Aviation Greases (Box 35, Folder 1683)
- Oxidation, Storage and Low Temperature Torque of Aviation Instrument Greases (Box 35, Folder 1684)
- Oxidation, Storage and Low Temperature Torque Tests on Grease Packed Bearings (Box 35, Folder 1685)
- Evaluation of the Oxidation of Missile Greases (Box 35, Folder 1686)
- Evaluation of the Oxidation of Missile Greases (Box 35, Folder 1687)
- Analysis of Gycol in Motor Oil, Demonstration (Box 35, Folder 1688)
- Nail Withdrawal Tests on Simpson Super-Strong Insulating Sheathing (Box 35, Folder 1689)
- Nail Withdrawal Tests on 1/2" Simpson Super-Strong Insulating Sheathing (Box 35, Folder 1690)
- Photographs for Simpson Timber Company (Box 35, Folder 1691)
- ** Moisture Permability Test (Permeability??) (Box 35, Folder 1692)
- Investigation of Redwood and Douglas Fir for Particle Board (Box 35, Folder 1693)
- Amenability Tests of Mattagami Zinc Calcine for the Electro-lytic Process (Box 35, Folder 1694)
- Amenability Tests of Mattagami Zinc Calcine for the Electro- lytic Process (Box 35, Folder 1695)
- Concentration Test on Uranium Bearing Ore (Box 35, Folder 1696)
- Sampling, Sample Preparation and Assaying for Uranium (Box 35, Folder 1697)
- Sampling Screening, Sample Preparation and Assaying Uranium Ore (Box 35, Folder 1698)
- Sampling Screening, Sample Preparation and Assaying Uranium Ore (Box 35, Folder 1699)
- Preparation of Uranium Ore Samples (Box 35, Folder 1700)
- ** Rocking Tests on 1/2" Insulation Sheathing (Box 35, Folder 1701)
- ** Rocking Tests on Simpson Insulation Sheathing (Racking??) (Box 35, Folder 1702)
- Nail Withdrawal Tests on Simpson Super-Strong Insulation Board Sheathing (Box 35, Folder 1703)
- Mt. Vernon Water Distribution Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1704)
- Arson Case (Farmers Market Spokane) (Box 35, Folder 1705)
- Oil and Gas Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1706)
- Investigation of the Angela Archer Case: Arson-Murder Comparison of Gasoline (Box 35, Folder 1707)
- Water Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1708)
- Preliminary Statistical Analysis of Weather Modification in S.W. Washigton and N.W. Oregon (Box 35, Folder 1709)
- Analysis of City of Vancouver Water Supply System (Box 35, Folder 1710)
- Fairbanks, Alaska, Water Distribution System Design Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1711)
- Fairbanks, Alaska, Water Distribution System Design Analysis (Box 35, Folder 1712)
- Water Distribution Analysis for Anacortes, Washington (Box 35, Folder 1713)
- Water Distribution Analysis for Anacortes, Washington (Box 35, Folder 1714)
- ** Investigation of Sask. Aspen for Flakeboard (Box 35, Folder 1715)
- ** Investigation of Sask. Aspen for Flakeboard (Box 35, Folder 1716)
- Investigation of Sask. Aspen for Flakeboard (Box 35, Folder 1717)
- Preparation of Barite Concentrate (Box 35, Folder 1718)
- The Beneficiation of Washington Barite Ore and the Production of Barium Sulphate and Carbonate (Box 35, Folder 1719)
- The Beneficiation of Washington Barite Ore and the Production of Barium Sulphate (Box 35, Folder 1720)
- Micro-particle Separation of Concentration and Tailings (Box 35, Folder 1721)
- Spectrographic Analysis in Uranium Ores (Box 35, Folder 1722)
- Shielded Room Measurements (Box 35, Folder 1723)
- E-9 Pivot Lubricant for Tally Register Corporation (Box 35, Folder 1724)
- Investigation of Lubrication of E-9 Pivot (Consulting) (Box 35, Folder 1725)
- Investigation of Lubrication of E-0 Pivot (Consulting) (Box 35, Folder 1726)
- Pivot Lubricant "A" for Tally Register Corporation (Box 35, Folder 1727)
- Preparation of Control Cables with Lubricant T-4 (Box 35, Folder 1728)
- Preparation of Control Cables with Lubricant T-4 (Box 35, Folder 1729)
- Police Investigation (Box 35, Folder 1730)